<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<!DOCTYPE EmailTemplate PUBLIC "sailpoint.dtd" "sailpoint.dtd">
<EmailTemplate name="Password Expiry Notification Remainder">
  <Body>Dear Ritesh,

Periodic changing of your $accountName Account Password is critical to secure your "SINGTEL”computer, accounts, and data.

1.            Windows Password Change

Your SINGTEL Windows account password will expire in xx days. Change your password immediately to prevent login failure. Your Windows account is also used to access your SINGTEL Email and LAN resources.

2.            Password Policy

Passwords must contain character combinations from at least three of the following categories (e.g. 2bn_oW):

              &gt; One alphabetic upper-case character (A-Z)

              &gt; One alphabetic lower-case character (a-z)

              &gt; One numeric character (0-9)

              &gt; One special character ((` ~ ! @ $ # %)

              &gt; Password must be minimally 8 alphanumeric characters in length

3.            Steps to Change Password

  WINDOWS COMPUTERS

---------------------------------------------------

a.            If you are in the SINGTEL office and connected to the corporate wireless network (SINGTEL@Work), press CTRL-ALT-DEL on your computer and choose “Change a password” to change your password.

     b. Working remotely and not connected to the corporate network follow the steps below:

1. Connect to the SINGTEL Virtual Private Network (VPN).

2. Press CTRL-ALT-DEL.

3. Click on “Change a password”.

4. After changing your password, press &lt;Windows Key&gt; + &lt;L&gt; together to lock the screen.

5. Enter the new password to unlock. This will allow the local cached credentials to sync with the Active Directory password.


   MACINTOSH / MACBOOK COMPUTERS

---------------------------------------------------

For Macintosh computers that HAVE JOINED the SINGTEL domain,

1. Connect to the corporate wireless network (SINGTEL@Work) or the SINGTEL VPN (if you are not in SINGTEL Hub).

2. Click on “System Preferences”.

3. Select “Users and Groups”.

4. Select “Change Password” beside your Profile Picture.

5. If you are on VPN, stay connected for at least 30 minutes. This will allow the new password to sync backend.


 For Macintosh computers that HAVE NOT JOINED the SINGTEL domain (i.e. unable to access SINGTEL@Work wireless network in SINGTEL Hub),

1. Connect to the SINGTEL VPN.

2. Access UAM (https://uam.sg.singtelgroup.net/aims/PS/LanguageSelect.aspx).

3. Stay connected to the VPN for at least 45 mins. This will allow the new password to sync backend.

4. McAfee Drive Protection Password

In addition to Windows, your device is also protected by McAfee Drive Protection. After changing your Windows account password, we also recommend that you change your McAfee Drive Protection password. Change the McAfee password by following these steps:

1. Restart your computer.

2. Select the “Change Password” box at the McAfee password entry page.

3. Enter your new password in the subsequent prompt.

Regards,

Singtel UAM Admin

This is a system generated notification, please do not reply.
    </Body>
  <Description>
      Email Template for notifying work item owners of new certifications.
    </Description>
  <Signature>
    <Inputs>
      <Argument name="identityName" type="string">
        <Description>The description property (also the name property) of the certification WorkItem.</Description>
      </Argument>
      <Argument name="accountName" type="string">
        <Description>The WorkItem object for the certification.</Description>
      </Argument>
      <Argument name="ownerName" type="string">
        <Description>The display name of the Identity that owns the certification.</Description>
      </Argument>
    </Inputs>
  </Signature>
  <Subject>Password Expiry Notification Remainder for : $accountName</Subject>
</EmailTemplate>